trythermocleanse.com 2010-04-22

# Terms and Conditions - ThermoCleanse

← back

Your private financial information is secure. Clean LifeStyle Ltd. will never divulge your personal, private financial information to anyone for any reason.

What This Privacy Policy Covers

  1. This policy covers how Clean LifeStyle Ltd. treats personal information that Clean LifeStyle Ltd. collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Clean LifeStyle Ltd. products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  2. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Clean LifeStyle Ltd. does not own or control, or to people that Clean LifeStyle Ltd. does not employ or manage. In addition, certain Clean LifeStyle Ltd. associated companies such as Visa, MasterCard and Telecom providers which have their own privacy policies.

## Information Collection and Use

### General

  1. Clean LifeStyle Ltd. collects personal information when you register with Clean LifeStyle Ltd., when you use Clean LifeStyle Ltd. products or services, when you visit Clean LifeStyle Ltd. pages or the pages of certain Clean LifeStyle Ltd. partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Clean LifeStyle Ltd. may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
  2. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, postal code, occupation, industry and we may also ask for your address, national identification number, and information about your assets. Once you register with Clean LifeStyle Ltd. and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  3. Clean LifeStyle Ltd. collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.
  4. Clean LifeStyle Ltd. automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Clean LifeStyle Ltd. cookie information, and the page you request.
  5. Clean LifeStyle Ltd. uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.
  6. This site uses ClickTale web analytics service. ClickTale may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as any text you type in this website. ClickTale does not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in this website. ClickTale does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use ClickTale services. For more information see Privacy Policy for Information Collected by the ClickTale Web Analytics Service. We are using the information collected by ClickTale service to improve our end user experience. You can choose to disable the Service at <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html>.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  1. Clean LifeStyle Ltd. does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies. Clean LifeStyle Ltd. Privacy Policy Your privacy is our first priority. about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies.

## Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

### General

  1. You can edit your Clean LifeStyle Ltd. Account Information at any time.
  2. New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.
  3. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Clean LifeStyle Ltd. service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Clean LifeStyle Ltd. Newsletter, that are considered part of your Clean LifeStyle Ltd. account
  4. You can delete your Clean LifeStyle Ltd. account by visiting our User Administration page.

### Confidentiality and Security

  1. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  2. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with regulations to protect personal information about you.
  3. To learn more about security, including the security steps we have taken and security steps you can take, please read Security at Clean LifeStyle Ltd.s.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

  1. Clean LifeStyle Ltd. may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Clean LifeStyle Ltd. account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

← back
